YouTube. YouTube, listen. Still
available. Listen. But better yet,
[music]
better yet,
the 360 Jeezy Xstyle Craft Trimmer
[music] is out right now. Listen, y'all
don't understand. Y'all don't know. It
was about 10 years ago, man. I was in
barber school. That was a long time. I
ain't going to lie. So, it it may not
hit. You know what I'm saying? But you
got to think about it. In barber school,
I didn't know that I would, you know
what I'm saying? Be connected with a
brand and have my name on a trimmer or a
[music] clipper. You know what I'm
saying? Like, you can't fathom that. You
know what I'm saying? I'm just saying,
man. When I was in barber school, I
would have never thought that I would
have my name on [music] a clipper or a
trimmer, but it's here. Stylecraft X360
GG trimmer. Let me show you what's
inside.
>> [music]
>> So, when you open it up, you'll
obviously see the trimmer, the one-year
warranty, the red bottom ring with a
mini oil and duster, [music] two red
rubber side grip, and a black motor
cover, a mini screwdriver, a USBC cord,
a black charging dock, and last but
[music] not least, the trimmer itself.
[music]
Now you guys can mix and match and
create your own version of this trimmer
[music] by changing the color of the
side grips, the bottom ring, and even
the motor cover. And if you guys have
more Stylecraftraft Blades, these fit on
those as well. All right, you guys,
that's what's in the box. Um, I did use
them in this video, so um, you can see
how it work. They're good. If you go to
my Instagram, too, I got plenty of
videos on there. If you want to pick
these up, you could go to
stylecraftus.com.
Link will be in the description. I'm
super excited, man. Stay tuned.
[music]
>> 360
clients. If you're wondering how to book
with me, I use an app called Book
[music] Me. Just download this app and
type in 360 Jeezy and you can find the
latest times and dates [singing] that I
have available. I set my schedule
[music] 2 weeks out, so don't think that
I'm booked out all year.
All right, you guys. To start off this
haircut, what I'm going to do is I'm
going to blow dry the hair and pick it
out at the same time. What this is doing
is softening the hair up so it's easier
for you to pick it out [music] without
making your client uncomfortable.
>> [music]
>> So, you always want to make sure you
comb the hair down and pick the hair out
first. That way, it's a lot easier for
you to fade. The fade will come out
looking a lot cleaner.
So, my client showed me a picture of
what he wanted and it was almost like a
burst [music] taper type of burst fade
look. Minimal C cups, [music] but um he
wanted that fade to be a little higher.
So, right now I'm setting in my bald
line and I'm doing it in a rainbow like
shape.
[music]
Now, grabbing my Stylecraft [music] X
360 Jeezy clippers with the lever open
and I'm going up about a/ inch. Making
sure I keep that rainbow like shape
consistent.
[music]
Now putting on my zero guard with the
lever open. I'm going up in a flick
[music] out motion. Kind of a scoop out
motion cuz I don't want to make a harsh
guideline into that afro. So [music] I'm
just scooping out that way the
transition could kind of seamlessly run
through. Um but I'm making sure that
it's at that one guard length as much as
possible using my corners to make
[music] sure you know everything at the
bottom is at that length.
>> [music]
>> So now I'm going to close the lever
fully and freehand that top. Uh just
building that shape a little bit. And
then I'm going to get back to, you know,
blending down. [music]
>> [music]
>> Now, to get rid of that line that
separates [music] the the bulk from the
blend, uh what I did was is I combed
down um before I went with the one guard
[music] and went with the grain. Right?
This kind of eliminates that line
between the the sides and the bulk at
the top.
Now, just closing the lever on that one
guard. I'm just going to soften up that
middle line. Um, using my corners as
much as possible. [music]
Now, with the line softened up, I put on
my zero guard with the lever fully
closed. And in a flick out motion, I'm
flicking out that middle line. [music]
[music]
Now, there's two ways you could attack
this bottom line. Um, you can soften it
up just like I did that middle line um,
by setting the lever halfway,
softening it up and then setting it
closed and taking it out fully. [music]
Well, what I like to do is I like to
close the lever and then just adjust my
lever as I go up. But if you want to
stay consistent um, with the the the
style and how you take out the
guidelines, I would suggest for
beginners to soften it up first and
[music] then take it out.
So, I want to tell you guys this just to
be transparent. [music] Sometimes the
blend doesn't come out looking as good
as you want it, but you can't just sit
there and focus on, you know, detailing
and detailing and detailing so much. You
have to move on. So, right now, [music]
I'm just detailing. I'm using my mirror.
Um, the mirror shows you a different
perspective on the blend than just
seeing it head on.
Also, if you don't have access to a
mirror, look away. come back to the
blend, but don't spend so much time in
one area. Like move on and then later on
come back to the blend once things look
complete and [music] then start, you
know, detailing again. But detailing is
key. So don't don't don't stray away
from detailing, but it gets to a point
where you do have to move on for the
sake of time.
>> [music]
>> So, like I said, I'm going to move on
from the blend and I'm going to shape
the hair, getting it down to the length
that my client wants so I can get a
better understanding of what the outcome
is going to be. Right? So, [music] I
always start from the bottom, shape my
uh afro to the top cuz when you swing
your arms down from the top, it gives a
better circular motion [music] when you
do it that way.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Now, as far as the back goes, it's the
same exact [music] steps. Um, the only
difference is I feel like you have a lot
more room to work with, right? Um, if
you're a student or beginner, you're
going to want to memorize these
guidelines, right? That's going to help
you out on your speed. You don't want to
have to, you know, think [music] about
what to do next. You want to already
know. The guidelines is ball line, lever
open, one open. [music]
Debbulk the top, come back down, soften
up that that middle line with the one
guard closed. Then [music] take it out
fully with the zero guard closed, then
attack that bottom line. Either soften
it first or take it out and adjust the
lever as you go up and then detail.
So now I'm going to continue to shape
the rest of the hair that's on [music]
top, starting from the bottom to the
top.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
I'm also going to use my curve shears to
really detail this afro. Um, keep in
mind that I'm not done with this taper.
Like I said before, sometimes you just
got to move on. All right. I am going to
go back and detail more with this blend
so I can get it looking the way I want
[music] and and looking finished.
>> [music]
>> So, now I'm going to prep the front
line. I'm going to spray some alcohol on
on a neck strip and wipe down my
client's forehead [music] just so I
could get rid of all the oils. Right.
So, I did go ahead and detail that
blend. I did it off camera. Um, but
yeah, as you can see, the blend is nice
and, you know, you know, graduate. So,
I'm just going to continue to clean the
skin with this alcohol, spray some
hairspray on my client's hair just to
lock everything in.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat.
[music]
Heat. [music]
You get your production. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> So, I'm not going to razor line my
client. I don't want to irritate his
skin. But what I will do to make it pop,
make that lineup pop. So, I'm going to
use the Barber Magic pencil, draw on the
hairline, um, and then spray some, uh,
oil sheen on it, [music] and then push
that that Barber magic pencil with my
trimmers up to the line. That way,
you'll still get that that razor kind of
I don't know what it's called. It's like
a like a thin razor line ash [music]
mark. You know what I'm saying? You're
still going to get that with this. So,
yeah.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Listen, let me tell you why they call me
360. When they sit in my chair, I spin
them in a full 360 and have them feeling
LIKE
>> I WOULD NEVER [screaming] IN MY LIFE
CHEAT ON MY BARBER AGAIN. YOUTUBE, this
is [music] the cut. And if you like it,
make sure you give it a thumbs up. If
you're new to my channel, please [music]
hit that subscribe button. Also, Hustle
Dreams Production, that's my brother. He
does on my beat. His YouTube channel
[music] will be linked in the
description below. Make sure you guys go
give him a follow. Also, if you want to
know where you can find any tools that
you seen in this [music] video, links
will be in the description below.
Otherwise, you guys can follow me on
Instagram and Tik Tok. My Tik Tok is
official 360 Jeezy [music] and my
Instagram is 360 Jeezy. But it's your
boy 360 Jeezy and I'm out of here.
[music]
>> [music]